字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
为了阻止邪恶极速者萨维塔
In an attempt to stop the evil speedster Savitar,
我不小心闯入了未来
I was accidentally thrust into the future,
看到他杀死了我心爱的女人
and I saw him murder the woman I love.
但是我不会再让这事发生了
But I won't let that happen.
我会尽我一切的努力来改变未来
I'm going to do everything in my power to change the future,
而我是唯一来得及拯救她的人
and I'm the only one fast enough to keep her alive.
我就是  闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
我把魔法石丢到神速力里之后
When I threw the Philosopher's Stone into the Speed Force,
我偶然地跑入了未来
I accidentally ran into the future.
我看到萨维塔杀了你
I saw Savitar murder you.
没法跑得那么快去救你
I wasn't fast enough to save you.
我们不能独自面对这事  巴里
We can't do this alone, Barry.
不如来加入我们
Why don't you come work with us?
你可以帮闪电侠小组打击超能力者
You can help Team Flash fight meta-humans.
欢迎加入我们
Welcome to the team.
如果他的能力
If his powers are linked to the energy
和那种联系起多宇宙的能量相关联
that ties together the multiverse...
那么他就能在任何地球上打开缺口
He can open a breach to any Earth he wants.
关于打击坏人不会告诉你的是
The thing they never tell you about fighting villains
没有事情一成不变
is that nothing ever stays the same.
你越努力铲除坏人
The harder you work to take down the bad guys,
他们越猖狂
the more they up their game.
先生们
Gentlemen,
欢迎来到犯罪未来时
welcome to the future of crime.
就连军队也还没有这些
Not even the military has these yet.
看样子圣诞节提前来了
Looks like Christmas came early.
你知道唯一的问题是什么吗
You know what the only problem is?
你们上了圣诞老人的惩罚名单
You're on Santa's naughty list.
圣诞节取消了
Christmas is canceled.
幸运的是  我们团队有自己的秘密武器
Fortunately, our team has a secret weapon of its own:
科学的化身  行动的化身
a man of science, a man of action,
这个人就是
and that man's name
HR·威尔斯
is H.R. Wells.
看看谁拿着涡旋加农炮
Look who has a vortex cannon.
HR
H.R.?
随着我给力的涡旋加农炮的一击
With a blast from my trusty vortex cannon,
-我了结了歹徒  -HR
- I dispatch the miscreant-- - H.R.
-在呢  -巴里需要帮助
- Hey, yep, here we are. - Barry needs help.
-巴里需要帮助  -闪电小子呢
- Yeah, Barry needs help. - Where's Kid Flash?
他在路上  你在路上吗
He's on his way. Are you on your way?
楔石城大桥需要帮忙
They need you at Keystone Bridge.
你们每次行动都这么混乱吗
Surely all your adventures are not this disorganized?
疯狂中自有章法
There's a method to the madness, mate.
看着学
Watch and learn.
电帮朝北走了
The Electric Gang is headed north.
你得在他们上高速之前截住他们
You gotta cut 'em off before they reach the freeway.
你想怎么玩
How you wanna play this?
我有个主意
I have an idea.
注意了
Eyes up!
他来了
Here he comes.
只有红的那个
Just the red one.
干得漂亮
Nice work.
他们都昏倒了
They're out cold.
好了  小子们
Okay, boys.
他们救了我们
They saved us.
They saved us!
你是谁
Who are you?
我是闪电小子
I'm Kid Flash.
加油  美洲豹  加油
我的天  可以跟你合影吗
Oh, my gosh. Can we get your picture?
可以
Yes.
好了  再见
Okay. Bye.
加油  闪电小子  加油
Go Kid Flash! Go Kid Flash!
闪电侠
第三季
第十一集
干得漂亮
Nice save!
我都写不出这么精彩的剧情
Could not have scripted it better myself.
谢了
Thanks.
主要是巴里干了重活
Barry did most of the heavy lifting.
-BA -是的  精彩  小子们
- B.A. - Yes, bravo, boys.
虽然我至少找到了六种方法
Although I did find at least six ways
你们可以做得更加高效
you could have done it more efficiently,
就说说
just--just saying.
那辆车上都是火辣的啦啦队员
I mean, the bus load of hot cheerleaders
看来是喜欢我们做事的方式
seemed like the way that we did things.
这事要写到书里
Oh, that's going in the book. You know what?
我要喝完了  我给你在中城吉特斯
I'm running low; let me buy you a cup of coffee
买杯咖啡
over at CC Jitters.
-邦德  你来吗  -不了  谢谢
- Bond, are you coming? - No, thank you.
所以到底有多少火辣的啦啦队员
So exactly how many hot cheerleaders?
我是个好孩子
I was a good boy.
他一直期待这样
You know, he's just been looking forward to this
他挺享受的
for a long time; he's enjoying the moment.
我很高兴有你照应着他
Well, I'm glad you have his back.
我们互相照应
We have each other's back.
有他一起实在是很棒
It's actually been really nice having him out there.
我想问你
Hey, I meant to ask you.
当你追到电帮时
When you found the Electric Gang,
你看到他们和什么人见面了吗
did you see them meeting with anyone else?
-比如说呢  -有传言说
- Like who? - Well, word on the street is,
城里来了个新军火商
there is a new arms dealer in town
有渠道搞到像掠夺用过的
with access to sophisticated weaponry
精密武器
like the gun that Plunder used.
你不觉得这是警察
Don't you think that's something
要处理的事情吗
for the police to handle?
我依然是一名记者  巴里
I'm still a journalist, Barry.
我不能因为你看到的就足不出户
I can't hide from the world because of what you saw.
回家见
See you at home.
不能失去她  西斯科
Can't lose her, Cisco.
拜托告诉我你找到了改变未来的方法
Please tell me you found a way to change the future.
我们找到了改变未来的方法
We found a way to change the future.
说真的吗
Did you really?
没有  但是我和凯特琳找到了方法再现
No, but Caitlin and I did find a way to map it.
你会喜欢的  跟我来
You're gonna love this. Follow me.
朱利安建议我们3D复原
Julian suggested we make a 3-D reconstruction
我们所见的未来场景
of the scene from the future exactly as we saw it.
用玩具
With toys.
用什么不是重点
The medium's not important.
多谢  注意看  巴里
Thank you. Eye on the ball, Barry.
这是我吗
Is this me?
为什么是个宇航员
Why is he an astronaut?
注意看  巴里  好吗
Eye on the ball, Barry, okay?
这立体模型告诉我们
Now, this diorama tells us
如果你想从萨维塔手里救下爱瑞丝
you need to cover this distance
就得在0.21秒内
in less than 0.21 seconds
跑过这段距离
if you want to save Iris from Savitar.
你们认为呢
What do you guys think?
认为你的计划是不可能的
Think what you're proposing is impossible.
-因此  你会失败  -为什么
- Therefore, you will fail. - Why?
也许多元宇宙对我来说是新的概念
Multi-universe is maybe a new concept to me,
但是数学不是
but mathematics is not.
注意看  艾伦
Pay attention, Allen.
这是你的速度时间线
This is your speed timeline.
这是你第一次获得
This is your maximum velocity
超能力时的速度极值
when you first acquired your powers.
这是你现在的最大速度
This is your current top speed,
而这是你在五月要在
and this is where you need to be in May
0.21秒内达到的速度
to cover that distance in 0.21 seconds.
根据你现在的速度提升
At your current rate of improvement,
不可能
impossible.
谢你鼓舞士气  教练
Thank you for that rousing pep talk, coach.
好吧  你休息一下吧
Okay, why don't you take a knee?
我们在这照看着呢
I think we got it covered here.
看起来是
It looks like it.
实际上我要回中城警局
I actually have to be back at CCPD.
你也是
As do you.
再见
Cheerio.
他确实想帮忙
He really does want to help
只是方式毒舌又不体贴
in his own snobbish, thoughtless way.
他说得对
He is right.
他确实有点混蛋
I mean, he's kind of a dick about it,
但是你不能反驳他的计算
but you can't argue with his math.
好吧  我们找别的方法解决
Okay, well, then, we'll find another way to make this work.
必须解决
We need to.
爱瑞丝不能死
Iris isn't gonna die.
多谢了
Thank you very much.
找到你了
Gotcha.
不许动
Freeze!
你怎么进来的
How'd you get in here?
有句话这么说
You know what they say.
一扇门关闭了
Every time a door closes...
一扇窗户会打开
a window opens.
中城吉特斯
巴里
Barry.
什么都没丢
Nothing's missing.
-是的  -钱还在收银机里
- Nope. - Cash is still in the register.
保险箱也没被人碰过
Safe's not touched.
看来为了在深夜喝杯咖啡
I mean, it seems like a lot to go through
费了很大劲才闯进去
to just get a late night cup of coffee, right?
肯定是超能力者所为
Yeah, it's definitely a meta.
我会让朱利安查他的超能力者资料库
I'll have Julian look into his meta database,
但是我觉得这是个新人
but I think this is someone new.
新来的危险人物
New and dangerous.
没有什么是闪电侠和闪电小子应付不来的
Well, it's nothing that The Flash and Kid Flash can't handle.
我的两个超级英雄小子
My two superhero boys.
他做得很好
He is doing great.
说到我的孩子
Speaking of my kids,
爱瑞丝  她有没有和你说
Iris, she tell you about this
她在报道的军火商新闻
arms dealer story she's following?
她说过
Yeah, she's mentioned it.
既然你现在是她的同居男友
Well, now that you're her live-in boyfriend,
你能照看她
could you look out for her
也许让她别插手太多吗
and maybe get her to back off a bit?
因为这不是她该独自一人去做的事
Because this isn't something she should be doing on her own.
同意  我会试试
I agree. I'm trying.
除此之前  她没什么事吧
She seem... okay to you, otherwise?
没  为什么这么问  你觉得有事吗
Yeah, why? Do you not think so?
如果你俩有什么问题
If you guys got something going on,
我希望你能和我聊聊
I hope you know you can talk to me.
我知道  乔
Yeah, I know, Joe.
谢谢  我...  我们
Thank you-- I -- we're...
我俩都很好
both doing great.
那好
Okay.
-晚点聊  -好
- Talk to you later. - Yeah.
这是吉特斯的监控录像
So this is the footage from Jitters
应该能确认新超能力者的身份
that should help us ID our new meta.
黑人女子  真是"缩小"了范围
Brunette? That really narrows it down.
我会弄清晰点的
Mm, I'll clean that up.
看看那屏幕上的照片多清晰
Oh, look how clear the picture is on that screen.
因为照片不是来自吉特斯的
That's 'cause that's not from Jitters.
是我们的安全监控录像
That's our security footage.
HR·威尔斯
H.R. Wells.
我知道你在里面
I know you're in there.
如果不想惹麻烦  就乖乖地走出来
Come quietly if you don't want trouble.
HR  她怎么会认识你
H.R., how does she know you?
快说  这位漂亮的闯入者是谁
Talk. Who is this... gorgeous intruder?
她叫吉普赛
Her name is Gypsy,
她在我的地球上被称为回收者
and she's what's known on my Earth as a collector.
她都回收些什么
What is she collecting?
她是来回收我的
She's come to collect, you know, me.
-哪里疼  -到处都疼
- Where does it hurt? - Oh, everywhere.
你能用震波
You can vibe?
我喜欢
Oh, I like it.
别轻举妄动
Slow down there.
我们像两个成年人一样好好聊聊
Let's just talk about this, like two adults,
边喝咖啡  如果你想  吃晚饭也行
over coffee, or maybe dinner, if you prefer that.
如果喜欢泰国菜  路前面有家好吃的泰国餐厅
There's a great Thai place up the road, if you like Thai.
对了  我叫西斯科  你就是吉普赛
I'm Cisco, by the way. You must be Gypsy.
很高兴见到你
It's nice to meet you.
你在约她吗
Are you asking her on a date?
你逗我呢
Are you kidding me?
我在谈判
I am negotiating.
你给我看了你招式
Well, you showed me yours.
我也要给你看我的才公平
Only fair I show you mine.
西斯科
Cisco!
女士  请你离开这栋楼
Ma'am, I'm gonna have to ask you to leave the building.
极速者
Speedster.
这下好玩了
That's fun.
我也喜欢玩
I like to have fun too.
看来你对自己的超能力还了解得不多
I see you've got a lot to learn about your power.
没错  就像这样
Yeah. Like that.
你怎么做到的  好酷
How do you do that? That's cool.
你们窝藏逃犯躲避审判
You're harboring a fugitive from justice.
我们的世界严格禁止维度间穿越
Our world has a strict ban on inter-dimensional travel.
他来的时候就知道了
He knew that when he came here.
-所以你追踪他到这  -老实话  很容易
- So you tracked him here? - Honestly, it wasn't that hard.
尤其是他在一章章地广播
Not when he's beaming "H.R. Wells'
《HR·威尔斯多元宇宙冒险记》
Adventures in the Multiverse" back chapter by chapter.
不管HR做了什么
You know what? Whatever H.R. did,
你不能就这样过来强行带走他
you can't just come here and take him by force.
除非你打倒我们
Not without going through us.
如果我真要打倒你们
If I really wanted to go through you,
你们就全死了
you would all be dead.
我现在已经锁定你了
I've got a lock on you now.
你是逃不掉的
There is no getting away.
给你一小时解决你的事
You've got an hour to get your affairs in order,
然后你要跟我回去
and then you are coming back with me.
拜拜  西斯科
Adios, Cisco.
华丽退场
What an exit.
"正当三藩西斯科扔出他华丽的锁  仰天一笑
"As Francisco threw back his lustrous locks and laughed,
我概述了化解那个狂暴生物的计划"
I outlined my plan for neutralizing the rampaging creature."
这段写了好几页
It goes on like this for pages.
他一直在广播这些
He's been broadcasting this
既不告知我们  也没征求同意
without our knowledge or permission,
一直在给他自己营造英雄形象
all the while making himself the hero.
每本小说都需要一个中心人物
Yeah, every book needs a central protagonist
读者才会想要花钱买书
that the audience can invest in.
我本该和巴里一起走的
I would have gone with Barry.
巴里
Barry?
西斯科  刚才是怎么回事
Cisco, what was that back there?
先是金色滑翔者  现在到她
First Golden Glider and now her?
谁吸引我  我控制不了
I can't help who I'm attracted to,
即使她是
even if it is the...
性感  极其致命的尤物
sexy, intense, deadly ones.
所以她带你回地球十九
So she takes you back to Earth-19,
然后怎样  你交罚款吗
and, what, you pay a fine?
在我地球上
The punishment for
对于非法穿越缺口的处罚是
an unauthorized breach travel on my Earth...
处死
it's death.
Death?
大约二十四五年前  附近的地球
About 24, 25 years ago, a neighboring Earth
从缺口入侵了我们的星球
invaded our planet through a breach
几乎毁了那里
and almost destroyed the place.
所以为了防止旧事重演
So to prevent it from happening again,
他们禁止了所有维度间穿越
they banned all inter-dimensional travel.
然后设置了回收者
And then they put the collectors in place
来惩罚我们当中想要违反禁令的人
to punish those of us who violated the ban.
我只是没想到她会追踪到我
I just didn't think that she'd track me down.
那你为什么冒死来到这里
So why would you risk your life by coming here?
我要收拾东西了
I-- I'm gonna get packing.
HR该勇敢地面对惩罚了
It's time for H.R. to face the music.
各位  我知道HR很烦人
Guys, I know H.R. can be annoying,
但是不至于要死
but he doesn't deserve to die.
不同的地球  不同的道德标准
Different Earth, different morality.
但是他并没有回去  我看到他了
But he doesn't go back. I saw him.
在未来和我  爱瑞丝  还有萨维塔一起
In the future, with me and Iris and Savitar, he was there.
这肯定意味着我们没让她带他走
I mean, that must mean we don't let her take him back.
也许吧
Maybe we do.
也许让他回到自己的地球
Maybe by letting him go back to his Earth,
就改变了你的未来
it changes your future
阻止爱瑞丝死去
and prevents Iris' death.
我要去见她
I gotta go see her.
中城新闻图报
你就这样让这女人带走HR吗
Are you just gonna let this woman take H.R.?
我不知道
I don't know.
不  我只是
No. I just...
但愿我知道这样是否能有所改变
I wish I knew if it would make a difference.
我是说  如果他回去了  事情没变呢
You know, I mean, what if he goes and nothing changes?
我们怎么知道现在的行动是否会影响未来
How do we ever know if our actions now impact the future?
是啊
Yeah.
有时我希望我们能有些普通人的问题
You know, sometimes I wish we had normal-people problems.
那样该有多好
Yeah, that would be nice.
你没和乔说未来的事吧
Hey, you didn't tell Joe about the future, did you?
没  当然没说
No, of course not.
我最不希望他担心
The last thing I need is for him to worry about
一件四个月后都未必会发生的事
something four months away that might not happen.
绝对不会发生的
That won't happen.
也许在这个时候
Maybe in the meantime,
你能否别再报道军火商的新闻
you could let this arms dealer thing go?
天呐  我爸又让你来劝我了
Oh, God, did my dad put you up to this too?
不  他不必让我来
No, he didn't have to.
-巴里  这... -不  对不起
- Barry, look, this-- - No, look, I'm sorry.
我不是想要阻止你去做你的工作
I'm not trying to keep you from doing your job, okay?
但是当我们全都集中在HR的事情上
But when we're all focused on this H.R. thing
尽力阻止未来的时候
and trying to prevent the future.
我们真的还需要更多的麻烦吗
I mean, do we really need to go looking for more trouble?
求求你
Please?
好吧  我不报道了
Okay, I'll drop it.
真的吗  这么简单
Really? Just like that?
是的
Um, yes.
有时候我是听你话的  知道吗
Sometimes I do listen to you, you know?
我之前可没这经历
That hasn't been my experience.
闭嘴吧
Shut up.
好了  等会见
All right. I'll see you later.
-好  再见  -谢谢
- 'Kay, bye. - Thank you.
你就不会跑腻吗
Don't you get tired of running?
是这样的  我想跑步
That's the thing, running just
能让我的头脑清醒一些
sort of keeps my mind off of things, I guess.
肯定感觉很棒
Must be an amazing feeling.
是很棒
It is.
搞大新闻能给我很棒的感觉
You know, cracking a big story gives me an amazing feeling.
我想我找到了个大新闻
And...I think I'm onto one.
是那个军火商的事吗
Oh, that, uh, arms dealer thing?
你怎么知道那事的
How do you know about that?
因为爸爸和巴里都想让你放弃那事
Because both Dad and Barry want you to lay off of it.
"死亡愿望"这话被他们说了很多次
The phrase "Death wish" got tossed around a lot by them.
我没什么死亡愿望
Okay, I do not have a death wish.
我只是想伸张正义
I just want to see justice done
就像这楼里的其他人
like everyone else in this building.
我懂  但这很危险  爱瑞丝
I get that, but it is dangerous, Iris.
沃利  这能有多危险
Wally, how dangerous could it be?
我的死期在五月
I don't die till May.
巴里说在闪点里  我和你
Barry said that in Flashpoint, you and I
是姐弟打击罪犯小分队
were a brother-sister crime-fighting team.
不如让我们重现那个现实
I say we make that a reality again.
我们不该先问问巴里吗
Shouldn't we ask Barry first?
不  这是你我之间的事  沃利
No, this is just between us, Wally.
我们能一起做这事
We can do this together.
你知道我会最想念这地球的什么吗
Do you know what I'm really gonna miss about this Earth?
我不知道  肥皂剧
I don't know. Uh... Soap operas.
我是说  一个又复杂又长的故事
I mean, a long, winding story
每天以一小时的章节播出
served up daily in hour-long chapters?
你还没回答凯特琳的问题
You never answered Caitlin's question.
为什么我在薯条里放芥末吗
Oh, about why I put mustard on my fries?
你为什么要冒着生命危险来到这里
Why you risked your life to come here.
那个
That.
我照了个镜子
I looked in a mirror.
我没懂
I don't follow.
在我的地球上
Look, on my Earth,
我有名气和权力
I had fame and power.
我受尊敬
I had respect.
我曾是"HR·威尔斯"
I was "H.R. Wells."
但当我照镜子的时候
But when I looked in the mirror,
我知道真相
I knew the truth.
而真相是
And the truth was...
我微不足道
I didn't matter.
我是个骗子
I was a fraud.
所以我才来到这个地球
That is why I came to this Earth,
这样我可以重写我的故事  毫不夸张
so I could rewrite my story, both literally and figuratively.
你肯定能做些什么  HR
There's gotta be something you can do, H.R.
没有
There's not.
你就不能雇个律师  上诉一下
You can't hire a lawyer? Appeal the case?
我无能为力  BA
There's nothing I can do, B.A.!
我不是想和你杠
I don't mean to snap at you.
就是我没什么选择  好吗
It just--I don't have any options here, all right?
除非  当然  我请求
Unless, of course, I appeal for
比武审判
trial by combat.
伙计们  吉普赛来了
Guys, Gypsy's here.
总是那么守时
Always so punctual.
真让我吃惊
I'm impressed!
我还以为你又要逃跑了呢
Thought you'd try and flee again.
是时候走了
Time to go.
好吧
All right.
吉普赛
Gypsy,
带我回家吧
take me home.
等等
Wait.
你不能带走他
You're not taking him anywhere.
-什么  -为什么
- What? - Why not?
因为我挑战你进行比武审判
Because I challenge you to trial by combat.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我挑战她进行比武审判
I'm challenging her to trial by combat.
不不  他没有
No, no, he isn't.
是我  我要和你斗
Okay, I am. I'm gonna fight you.
可是那位先说的
Well, that one spoke first.
什么  那也是规则吗
What? That's like a real rule?
以地球19的法律  我挑战你对
By the laws of Earth-19, I hereby challenge you
HR·威尔斯的控制权
for possession of H.R. Wells.
如果你愿意  我们可以换个方式
If you want, we can solve this another way.
这里有个不错的喝酒地方
There's a great spot for drinks--
你知道比武审判是至死方休吧
You realize trial by combat is to the death?
没错  失败者必死
Yeah. For the loser.
听着  你想要他
Listen, you want him?
你用实力赢得他
You're gonna have to come and claim him.
《指环王》第一部的经典台词
是亚玟说的  亚玟的话
That's Arwen. That's--Arwen.
我猜你还需要惯例的24小时来准备
I take it you also want the customary 24 hours to prepare?
-我想不想要惯例  -你想要
- Do I want the customary... - Yes, you do.
我确实想要使用
I would love to take advantage
惯例的24小时  如果你不介意
of the customary 24 hours, if you don't mind.
好吧
Very well.
一天
One day.
到时见
See you then.
她会杀了我  对吧
She's gonna kill me, isn't she?
她很厉害
She's good.
她很棒
She's great.
我是说  吉普赛是我地球上的传奇
I mean, Gypsy is a legend on my Earth.
那你到底为什么同意和她斗呢
So why, exactly, did you agree to fight her?
我不知道
I don't know.
你做了我们都会做的事
You did what any of us would have done.
我可能不会这么做  说实话
I might not have done it, just being honest.
好吧  和我坦白吧
Okay, all right. Lay it out for me.
我获胜的机率有多少  从一到十
What are my chances here, scale of one to ten?
她一定会杀了你
She's gonna kill you.
应该肯定是个"一"  伙计
It's a pretty solid "One," mate.
你有和吉普赛一样的超能力吧
You have the same powers Gypsy does, right?
我是说  她能做的你都能做
I mean, she's not doing anything you can't do.
做得更好  我是说  她就是更厉害点
Much better--look, I mean, she's doing it just much better.
你能办到的  好吗
You can do this, okay?
你只需要一点练习和一点自信
You just need a little practice and a little confidence.
我们都会帮助你的  好吗
And we're all gonna help you with that, right?
-是的  -是啊  是啊
- Yes. - Uh, sure, sure, yeah.
-是的  -没错
- Yes. - Yeah.
我相信你的  好吗
I believe in you, all right?
你能打败她
You can beat her.
听着  我有些点子
Listen, I have some ideas
在这里开设几个训练课程
for a training regimen I can set up in here.
凯特琳  你不如去
Caitlin, why don't you get
医务室做些准备
the medical bay prepared in the meantime?
什么  为什么  为什么她要
What? Well, why does--why does she
去准备医务室
need to set up the-the medical bay?
当你
For when you...
打败她时  当你打败她
beat her, when you beat her,
她可能  可能会需要医疗救护
she's gonna--she's gonna need medical attention.
因为你会打败她  我非常有信心
'Cause you will beat her, I have every faith
你一定会打败她
that you're going to beat her.
我们得加强你的人际交往技巧
We need to work on your interpersonal skills.
我在努力
I was really trying.
-有人打败过她吗  -有啊
- Has anyone ever beat her? - Yeah.
没有
No.
好吧
Oh, okay.
好吧  我正式进入了一个正常舒适的
Well, I've officially reached a nice, comfortable level
赤裸裸恐慌水平
of just straight-up panic.
我说  你都不喜欢我
I mean, you don't even like me.
为什么要为我冒生命危险
Why would you risk your life for me?
你听到巴里说的了  我们这里就这样
Well, you heard Barry. It's what we do around here.
别这样  为什么
Come on. Why?
你和其他的威尔斯们不同
You're not like the other Wellses.
你倒是一直在提醒我
Yeah, so you keep reminding me.
不  我是说  那两个都是天才
No, I mean, those two, they were geniuses.
我们依赖他们
We depended on them.
但对于你  角色对调了
But with you, the roles are reversed.
你依赖我们
You depend on us.
哈里森·威尔斯总是照顾我
Harrison Wells was always there for me,
我想以某种奇怪的方式  我就是...
so I guess in some weird way, I just...
我想要照顾哈里森·威尔斯
I want to be there for Harrison Wells.
-算了... -好吧
- Anyway... - Yeah.
中城警局
你来这里干什么
So what are we doing here?
我以为你不想让爸爸知道
I thought you didn't want Dad to know
我们在调查军火商
we're going after this arms dealer.
是啊  我不想
Oh, yeah, no, I don't.
但实际上
But, um, actually,
我需要你找出他调查案子的文件
I need you to swipe his file on the case
给文件照相之后然后放回去
and photograph the pages and then put them back.
谢谢
Thanks.
什么
What?
爱瑞丝
Iris.
你是疯了吗
Have you lost your mind?
爸爸会杀了我们的
Dad will kill us.
不不  沃利  他不会的
No, no, Wally, he won't.
他根本不会意识到闪电小子去过
He won't even know that Kid Flash was there.
首先  你得告诉我为什么
First, you have to tell me why.
好吧
Okay, look.
我知道大家都下了很大的功夫
I know everyone is working really hard
去阻止萨维塔...
to prevent Savitar from...
是的
Yeah.
老实说  这可能是我在地球的最后几个月了
But, honestly, these could be my last few months on Earth.
你能不这么说吗
Can you not talk like that?
我只是实事求是  沃利
I'm just being realistic, Wally.
这是我的特权
I get to do that.
我想让我的生命有点意义
Look, I want my life to mean something,
而不仅仅是作为谁的女儿或姐姐
more than just a daughter or as a sister
或者女朋友
or as a girlfriend,
我想做记者该做的事
but as a reporter.
这篇报导可以帮我完成这个心愿
This story can do that.
可以证明我  爱瑞丝·韦斯特很重要
It can say that I, Iris West, mattered.
我的生活在有了个姐姐之前可简单得多
You know, my life was a lot easier before I had a sister.
但现在要好得多  不是吗
But it's a lot better now, isn't it?
来吧
Come on.
好吧
Okay.
我可以帮你弄到不敲门搜查令
I can get you the no-knock warrant,
但是  乔  这个人武装到牙齿了
but, Joe, this guy is armed to the teeth
天知道是些什么
with God only knows what.
你们要又快又狠地进到里面去
You're gonna have to move in there fast and hard.
"又快又狠"  好的  我有点...
"Fast and hard," okay, I kind of walked into that--
抱歉打搅一下
Hey. Sorry.
-嘿  亲爱的  -你好
- Hey, sweetheart. - Hi.
你好  爱瑞丝
Hi, Iris.
你好  很高兴见到你  塞西尔
Hi. Good to see you, Cecile.
爸  能占用一点你的时间
Um, Dad, can I borrow you for a second
来次父女间的谈话吗
for a little father-daughter talk?
我得去和辛格队长叙叙旧
I need to go catch up with Captain Singh,
我一会回来  好吗
so I will be back in a little while, yeah?
-很高兴看见你  -我也是
- It's good to see you. - Good to see you too.
怎么了  有什么事
So...what's up? How can I help you?
我能和你在那边谈一下吗
Can I talk to you for a second over here?
这个  就是
Uhh, yeah, so, um,
我想和你谈谈  我和巴里的事
I wanted to-- to speak to you about me and Barry.
你和巴里
You and Barry?
-是的  -好吧
- Yes. - Okay?
每对情侣都会有一阵子
So there comes a time in every couple's relationship
有个人会觉得两个人太爱彼此
when you realize that there is too much love for two people.
然后...
And...
这个时候  你打从心底知道
Uh, when that happens, you know in your heart
唯一的解决办法就是
that the only solution is
扩大一下家庭...
to make your family a little...bigger.
好吧  我需要缓一下
Okay, I'm gonna need a second.
爸  认真听我说
Dad, hey, hey, listen to me very closely.
这对我很重要
This is so important to me.
天啊
Oh, God.
-巴里喜欢狗还是猫  -什么
- Is Barry a dog or a cat person? - What?
是啊  他喜欢什么动物
Yeah, what kind of animal does he like?
因为我想和他养一只宠物
Because I was thinking about getting him a pet
而我真的不记得他喜欢什么了
and I don't really remember him having a preference.
天啊  你真是吓着我了
Oh, man, you had me going there for a second.
什么  你以为我在说什么
What, what did you think I was talking about?
没什么  没什么  我...
Nothing, nothing, I--
你想跟他养什么就养什么
you can get him any kind of animal you want
只要是四条腿的就行
as long as it has four legs.
好  很好的建议  四条腿的  知道了
Good, great advice, four legs, copy that.
谢谢你跟我谈心  好了  再见
Thanks for the chat. Okay, bye.
讨厌
Damn.
又朝错方向了  多少次了
Facing the wrong way again. How many is that?
-三次  -九次
- Three. - Nine.
-你能行的  -是啊
- You'll get there. - Yes.
希望能在剩下的21小时46分内成功
Hopefully in the next 21 hours and 46 minutes.
好吧  每当我去战斗的时候
All right, look, whenever I'm out there,
陷入恶战  我觉得自己不行了
I'm in a tough fight, I think maybe I don't have it,
我就会深呼吸
I just take a deep breath...
相信我的直觉
Trust my instincts.
相信我的直觉  很好
Trust my instincts, that's good.
很有帮助
That helps.
-他去哪了  -不知道
- Where'd he go? - I don't know.
各位
Guys?
我在这
Up here.
-我们去聊聊  -好吧
- Let--let's go talk. - All right.
我们不能让弗朗西斯科和吉普赛打
We can't let Francisco fight Gypsy,
如果打起来  他就死定了
because if he does, he is a dead man.
-你可不知道  -我知道
- You don't know that. - Oh, I know that.
你也知道  他也知道
You know that. He knows that.
-好吧  我明白了  -她也知道
- Okay, I get it. - She knows that.
我们都知道  所有人都知道
We know that; everybody knows--
那我们该怎么办
So what are we supposed to do?
我该在他们打起来前阻止她
We're supposed to stop her before she fights him.
如果知道她在那里就好办了
That would be great if we knew where she was.
-请说  -我知道她在哪里
- Yes? - I know where she is.
你怎么知道的
How?
上次她来的时候我用追踪器标记她了
I tagged her with a tracer last time she was here.
一位魔术师朋友告诉我
A magician friend told me
你让他们分了心  标记了...
you kind of distract 'em and tag--
-HR -我要知道她在哪里
- H.R. - I needed to know where she was
所以我能早她一步
so I could stay one step ahead of her.
她就在...
She is...
吉普赛
在滨水区
At the Waterfront.
你觉得怎么样  为了弗朗西斯科
What do you say? For Francisco?
好
All right.
这个世界也许是一滩原始的
This world may be a primitive,
未开化的死水
uncultured backwater,
但他们做的咖啡确实挺棒的
but they do make an excellent cup of coffee.
的确  你知道你该试试什么吗
That they do. You know what you gotta try?
你该试试巴西烘焙咖啡  新出的
You gotta try the Brazilian roast, it's new.
非常美味
It is so good.
或许我该带几袋子回去
Maybe I'll take a few bags back with me.
是的  明智的选择
Yeah, think that's wise.
你要我把你装在袋子里带回去吗
Will you be going back in a bag?
听着  那个孩子  弗朗西斯科
Look, that kid, Francisco,
他只是想保护我
he's just trying to protect me.
那他真是傻得可爱
Then he's as foolish as he is cute.
好吧  吉普赛
Okay, Gypsy.
我们回去吧
Let's go home.
BA
B.A.!
想得美
Nice try!
你觉得我没发现吗
You think I didn't see that coming?
住手  住手
Stop, stop!
-住手什么  -住手...
- Stop what? - Stop--
停止执法吗
Stop trying to enforce the law?
你是个罪犯
You are a criminal.
你能在这交到朋友是很不错
Now, it's great that you made friends here,
但这改变不了你撒了谎的事实
but that doesn't change the fact that you lied.
你违反我们最神圣的法律
You broke our most sacred laws,
现在是时候接受法律制裁了
and now it is time for you to face justice.
等下
Wait!
你还要通过西斯科那关
You still need to face Cisco.
不  我觉得这个小花招使他的申辩失效了
No, I think this little stunt forfeits his claim.
还有他的时间
And his time.
你刚不是说你相信法律吗
You just said you believe in the law, right?
我们犯了错
We made a mistake.
西斯科会坚持完成他与你的协议
Cisco will hold up his end of the deal.
他会的
He will.
你还真是把这些人骗得团团转
You have really pulled a number on these people
他们都愿意为你而死
if they would die for you.
告诉西斯科没法反悔了
Tell Cisco there is no backing out now.
在此之前他都要在我这作为抵押
I'll keep this one as insurance until then.
BA
B.A.
这可不妙
That's not good.
她把HR抓走了
She took H.R.?
她可以这么做吗
Can she do that?
我以为整个比武审判会有什么规则
I mean, I though this whole trial by combat thing had rules.
很明显在我们
Which apparently we broke
想先发制人时就已经违背了
when we tried to get the drop on her.
那可不太明智  对吧
Well, that wasn't very clever, was it?
言而有信  应该遵守规则
A deal's a deal. It should be honored.
知道吗  你说得对  朱利安
You know what? You're right, Julian.
言而有信
A deal is a deal.
我们达成一致的是我会接受训练
And our deal was that I would train
挑战吉普赛  但是我猜你们两个
so that I could fight Gypsy, but I guess you two
想背着我把我换下来
wanted to go behind my back and try to sub in?
我们没有背着你
We didn't go--
我们只是觉得也许你需要帮助
we just thought maybe you could use some help.
是吗  那你所谓的
Yeah? What happened to,
"西斯科  你可以打败她"呢
"Cisco, you can beat her"?
-你可以的  -  还有"我相信你"
- You can. - "I believe in you."
-我相信  -"相信你的直觉"
- I do. - "Trust your instincts."
好吧  现在
Well, right now,
我的直觉告诉我  我应该写下
my instincts are telling me I should be writing
我的遗愿和遗嘱  请允许我离开下
my last will and testament, so please excuse me.
西斯科  别...
Cisco, come--
要我去和他谈谈吗
Should I go talk to him?
不了  我...
No, I--
我去吧
I got it.
看上去不止我一个人需要
Looks like I'm not the only one
练习下人际交往技巧
who has to work on their interpersonal skills.
你要留心了
I'd be careful if I were you.
我们最不想看到我按下按键
Last thing we want is for me to touch a button
把你脑袋炸飞吧
and blow your head off, right?
因为我也不懂自己在做什么吧
'Cause I don't know what I'm doing, right?
你知道我没那么想
You know I don't think that.
对  你表达的方式
Yeah, well, you have a very,
非常非常奇怪
very strange way of showing it.
你是对的  哥们  抱歉
You're right, man. I'm sorry.
我也说不上  只是
I don't know. I just...
"速度提不上来"这件事
guess this whole "Not getting faster" thing,
让我很困扰
it just has me rattled.
之前我总是能做到  你知道的
I was always able to do it before, you know?
先是打败逆闪电  再打败极速  但是
I mean, against Reverse Flash and then against Zoom, but...
萨维塔完全不在一个水平
Savitar's on a whole other level.
知道我失败后他会对爱瑞丝做的事
And knowing what he'll do to Iris if I fail?
我恐怕只能
I'm afraid just...
设想我打不过吉普赛  HR会怎么样
thinking what's gonna happen to H.R. if I don't beat Gypsy.
但你才是英雄
But you, you're the hero. I mean,
一直以来你是怎么抗下这些压力的
how do you handle all this pressure all the time?
我就是全靠依赖你们
By just leaning on all of you guys.
我是说你们一直站在我身边
You know, I mean, you're always in my corner,
帮我直面恐惧
helping me face my fears.
害怕是正常的  相信我
And it is okay to be afraid. Trust me.
等你站出去了  我会陪着你
And when you are, I'll be there
站在你身边
in your corner.
好的  精彩的小演讲  艾伦
Yes, lovely little speech, Allen.
但拉蒙先生要打败
But what Mr. Ramon needs to defeat
他的维度间敌人
his inter-dimensional adversary
需要一项实际的策略
is a practical stratagem.
你走运了  我找到一个
Lucky for you, I found one.
这是吉普赛的招牌动作
This is Gypsy's signature move.
我称之为"缺口和爆炸"
I call it her "Breach and blast".
对  那个动作
Oh, yeah. That move.
你们看  在她进出缺口之前
You see just before she comes in and out of a breach,
她的双脚是离地的
her feet come off the ground.
在那一瞬间她是离地的
So for that split second she's off the ground,
她会失去平衡
she'll be off-balance.
对  就会不堪一击
Yes, and vulnerable.
在对战时你或许可以利用这点
It might behoove you to use this during the battle.
太好了  朱利安
This is great, Julian.
很高兴能帮到忙
Hmm, just glad I could be helpful.
岂止是帮忙  我去研究一下
This is...more than helpful. I gotta work on this.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - Cheers.
谢了
Thanks.
你确定就是这里吗
You sure this is the place?
-确定  -好
- Positive. - All right.
准备好端掉个军火商了吗
You ready to bust an arms dealer?
-给我个头版头条  -沃利  慢着
- Get me a front-page headline? - Wally, wait.
中城警局花了好几个月找这家伙
CCPD's been looking for this guy for months.
他可能有秘密的隧道网络
He might have some sort of secret tunnel network
帮他偷偷溜走
that helps him slip out and get away.
我来快速侦察一番
I should do a quick recon.
好  彻底侦察
Yeah. Thorough.
可不想错过什么  懂吗
We don't want to miss anything, okay?
很快回来  你懂的
Be back in a you-know-what.
非请勿进
私人场地
但愿你看到的没让你失望
Hope you like what you see,
因为这场"试映"的"票价"是你的命
'cause this sneak preview is gonna cost you your life.
是吗  我看未必
Yeah, I don't think so.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
这会把你身体打个窟窿
This'll rip a hole right through you.
人都有一死  对吧
Everyone's gotta go sometime, right?
我很肯定自己今天
And I am pretty sure today just...
还死不了
isn't my day.
搞什么  姐姐
What the hell, sis?
你是想自杀吗
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
天啊  好了  在中城警局看到你前
God, okay, look, we gotta get you out of here
你得离开这
before CCPD sees you.
没事  爸现在就像我的头号粉丝
Don't worry. Dad's, like, my biggest fan now.
我做这些他完全不会介意
He's totally cool with me doing stuff like this.
才怪  我非常介意
Hell no, I ain't cool with this.
你俩差点搞砸地检办公室花了数月
You two almost compromised a major CCPD sting operation
策划的中城警局重大突击圈套
that took the DA's office months to assemble.
人还是抓到了吧
You still got the guy, right?
重点不是这个  爱瑞丝
That is not the point, Iris.
重点是你带着你弟弟一起
The point is, you had you and your brother out there
以身犯险  为了什么
in danger, and for what?
新闻吗  还有你跑哪去了
A story? And where the hell were you?
爸  对我来说这不只是新闻
Dad, this is more than just a story for me.
对  可你差点吃了枪子
Yeah, which you almost got shot for.
天啊
Oh, God.
什么
What?
爱瑞丝
Iris.
你这是怎么了
What is going on with you?
乔  抱歉  我能跟你谈一谈吗
Joe, I'm sorry-- can I talk to you for a second?
很快回来
We'll be right back.
乔已经怀疑事情不对劲了
Joe already suspects something's up.
你这样不顾安危  只会让事情更明显
You going out there like that, it just hangs a bell on it.
这新闻将会改变人生  巴里
This story is going to change lives, Barry.
你凭什么觉得就你可以
Why do you think that you're the only one
冒生命危险去做好事
allowed to risk your life to do good?
我没有
I don't.
害怕未来很正常
It's okay to be afraid of the future.
但我不会让你死去
But I won't let you die.
我不害怕死亡  巴里  我不怕
I am not afraid to die, Barry, I'm not.
那是什么
Then what?
我害怕
I'm afraid...
如果我的下场和我妈妈一样呢
What if I end up just like my mom?
没留任何痕迹
Just gone without making a mark,
什么都没留下就走了
without leaving anything behind.
爱瑞丝  你妈妈
Iris, your mom,
并非什么都没留下
she left something behind.
她留下了英勇优秀的儿子
She left a brave, wonderful son
以及我深爱的女子
and the woman that I love.
好了吗
All right?
我不知道未来会怎样  谁都不知道
I don't know what the future holds, none of us do.
但我知道我们会共同面对
I know that we will face it together.
吉普赛把她的位置震波给我了
Gypsy just vibed me her location.
动手吧
Let's do this.
我认为我们地球上的文学评论家
I don't think the literary critics on our Earth
并不了解真正的畅销科幻爱情小说
would know a real sci-fi romance best seller
-除非让他们  -时间到  威尔斯
- unless it bit them in the-- - Time's up, Wells.
看来你所谓的朋友终究是个懦夫
Looks like your so-called friend is a coward after all.
他不是懦夫
He's not a coward.
他是我认识的最好的人之一
He's one of the finest men I've ever known.
这话说的没错
Oh, you're right about that!
我非常好
I'm fine as hell.
他来了
There he is.
没想到你会来
Didn't think you'd show.
我可不会错过跟你共度良宵
Oh, I wouldn't miss an evening with you,
那怕是一决胜负的时刻
even if it is for a showdown.
我会杀了你  西斯科
I will kill you, Cisco.
看看今晚死的是谁
We'll see who dies tonight.
但愿HR威尔斯获胜
To the victor goes H.R. Wells.
愿最厉害的震波获胜
May the best vibe win.
我也曾期望过你今晚不出现
Part of me was hoping you wouldn't show tonight.
你想怎么对决
How do you want to do this?
西部风格  背对背  走十步  转身开枪
"Westworld"-style, back to back, ten paces, turn and shoot?
不
No.
这可不是好兆头
This does not bode well.
西斯科能撑住的
Cisco can hold his own.
很悬
Hmm. Barely.
巴里  不能坐视不管
Barry, we can't let this happen.
要是他打不过她呢
What if he can't defeat her?
我不能再度插手
I can't interfere again.
我插手就会受罚  HR就死定了
If I do, then we forfeit. H.R.'s a dead man.
这样下去西斯科也死定了
At this rate, Cisco's gonna be the dead man.
姑娘
Ooh, girl!
有两下子
You done did it now!
比我想的要强
Stronger than I thought.
我只是在热身
I'm just getting warmed up.
好了  别说这些
Yeah, maybe not do that.
该把音量调到十一了[出大招]
Time to turn things up to 11.
[摇滚万岁]中主角打破常规
将音量调到十一
《摇滚万岁》
"Spinal Tap."
是我最爱的电影之一
That's, like, one of my favorite movies--
他们去哪了
Where did they go?
他们去哪都有可能
I--they could be anywhere by now.
去到任何宇宙
In any universe.
这是地球二
This is Earth-2.
你真可爱  但话太多
You're cute, but you talk too much.
你想耍阴招
Oh, you want to play dirty, huh?
那就来阴的
Let's play dirty.
真疼
That hurts.
这也好疼
That too.
是我还是这城市越来越奇怪了
Is it me, or is this city getting weirder?
真火热
Well, this is hot.
我认为你用调情来分散我的注意力
I think you're flirting with me to distract me
是因为你害怕了
'cause you're afraid.
我的回收记录完美无瑕
My collection record is flawless.
在这类裁判中我从未失手
In these trials, I am undefeated.
拜托
Oh, please.
谁都有软肋
Everybody's got a weakness.
哪怕是你
Even you.
说这话的人却害怕向所有人展示
Says the man afraid of showing everyone
他能够有多强大
how powerful he can be.
你跟我在相似的频率共振
You and I resonate on a similar frequency.
我可以感觉到
I can feel it.
但你被你的害怕和不安拖住了
Yet you allow your fear and insecurity to hold you back.
所以你会输
That's why you're gonna lose.
你觉得我这是被拖住了吗
Does this look like holding back to you?
-我可以做一整晚  -你怎么...
I could do this all night. - How did you--
下次搞好你的平衡  姑娘
You might want to work on your balance next time, girl.
承认吧
Admit it,
我赢了
I won.
-没错  -他赢了
- Yes! - He won.
-他做到了  -他赢了
- Yeah, he did. - He won.
棒
Yes!
她今天一定不在最佳状态
She must have been having an off day.
怎么了
What?
根据地球十九的法律
By the laws of Earth-19,
犯人由你处置
the prisoner is yours for the taking,
还有我的命
as is my life.
不不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no.
我们这里不是这样的
We don't roll like that around here.
起来吧
Come on.
在多元宇宙中  我...
In all the multiverse, I have...
未曾
never...
遇过像你这样的人  西斯科
met anyone like you, Cisco.
请叫我震波
Please, call me Vibe.
或者你可以叫我西斯科
Or--or you can call me Cisco.
你可以这么叫我
That's also allowed.
我只是个普通人
I'm just a regular guy.
只是个普通的...
Just a regular...
单身汉
single guy.
显示你一切正常
It says you're totally fine.
那么之后呢  回你的地球
So what happens now? Go back to your Earth?
告诉你所有的上级你在战斗中被打败了
Tell all your superiors that you were bested in battle,
所有对HR的指控都撤销了
all the charges against H.R. Are dropped.
不
No.
我告诉他们我杀了他
I tell them I killed him.
慢着  你说什么
Wait, what?
如果我空手而归  他们会知道我失败了
If I return empty-handed, they'll know I failed.
我不曾失败过
And I never fail.
直到今天
Until today.
好吧  如果
Okay, but if you
你告诉他们你杀了我  那我...
tell them that you killed me, then I--
你就不能回地球十九了
You will never go back to Earth-19,
永远不能
ever.
我们说定了吗
Do we have a deal?
好吧  我们说定了
Yeah. I guess we have a deal.
我在那里没有任何牵挂
I don't really have anything to go home for.
这里永远是你的家  HR
You'll always have a home here, H.R.
我知道你地球的咖啡作物
Listen, I know there's no coffee on your Earth
因枯萎病什么的而灭绝了
'cause of the whole Blight thing or whatever,
这些给你带回
but this--this is just an absurd
你地球的咖啡数量真是荒谬
amount of coffee you're bringing back to your Earth.
肯定是要违法的
That can't be legal.
你不说出去我也不会说
I mean, I won't tell if you won't.
对于坚持奉公守法的人来说
You know, for someone so fixated on enforcing the law,
你还真是心安理得的去犯法啊
you sure seem oddly at ease about breaking it.
某些人值得你为他
Well, I guess some laws are worth breaking
犯一些法
for the right person.
所以就此别过了
So this good-bye then?
暂且别过
For now.
好棒的退场方式
What an exit.
闪电离开
以现今世上速度最快的人来说
Okay, you know, for the fastest man alive,
你是最慢的读者
you are the slowest reader.
这是你的大新闻  我可不打算马虎扫过
Hey, this is your big article, I'm not gonna rush through it.
我说笑的  我已经读了五遍了
I'm just kidding. I read it five times already.
你把闪电小子塑造成
You sure sold the hell out of Kid Flash
中城的下一个超级救世主
as Central City's next super savior.
我相信沃利会很喜欢
I'm sure Wally's loving that.
我答应把头版给他
/Well, I did promise him the front page.
你觉得呢
But what do you think?
你觉得这有影响力吗
Do you think it'll make any difference?
闪电小子已经改变了我们看见的未来的一件事
Kid Flash already changed one thing that we saw in the future.
不  我说的是报道
No, I meant the article.
怎么了
What?
这个报道
The article?
你应该非常骄傲
I think you should be really proud.
这是一个...
It's the beginning of...
出色记者遗产的开端
an amazing journalistic legacy.
是吗
Really?
有多出色  像获得普利策奖一样出色吗
How amazing? Like Pulitzer amazing?
时间会证明一切
Time will tell.
我很抱歉  我...
Hey, I'm sorry. I--
你知道我发现了什么吗
Do you know what I realized?
萨维塔说他不管在哪儿
Savitar, he said that I trapped him
他都被我困住  你知道这表示什么吗
wherever he is; you know what that means?
表示我打败过他
Means I beat him.
我保证我还会再次打败他
And I'm gonna do it again, I promise.
所以别担心
So don't worry.
闪电侠会救你的
The Flash is gonna save you.
我的英雄
My hero.
他们没告诉你的是
The thing they never tell you
任何事都不会维持不变
is that nothing ever stays the same.
所以你越努力打败坏人
So the harder you work to take down the bad guys,
他们也变得越厉害
the more they up their game.
我很抱歉  不是故意打扰你的
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to interrupt.
不会
No.
只是来拿点东西...
Just had to grab some stuff for--
我以为你这份活已经完事了吧
I thought you were finished working with that stuff?
这个只是...我自己留用的
Oh, no, it's just, uh, this is just for me.
不  那本书...  你知道
No, the--the book, it-- you know,
记录我个人的成就感
my own personal sense of accomplishment.
好吧
Well,
你成就了许多
you've accomplished plenty.
我成就了什么  弗朗西斯科
What have I accomplished, Francisco?
其中一个就是
Well, for one,
你让我冒险救你
you got me to risk my life to save yours.
相信我  朋友  那是个不小的成就
And trust me, my friend, that is a huge accomplishment.
说到这...
Yeah, about that...
我想跟你说
I just want to say that
我很感激你为我做的事
I appreciate what you did for me.
这是朋友之间会做的事  对吧
Yeah, it's what we do for our friends, right?
而且  这只是我取得平衡的一种
Besides, it was a way for me to balance the scales.
取得平衡  好吧
Balance the scales, right.
你在说什么
What does that mean?
我在说
I just mean...
跟你有同一张脸的人
I can't tell you the amount of times
在我遭遇你这种困境时在我身边
that I've been in your shoes and a man with your face
扶持了我无数次
has made me feel better.
说到这  我很...
Yeah, about that, I would--
我很乐意听你分享
I would love if you could share
我二重身的一些事
some of my doppelganger's knowledge.
我想知道更聪明版的我的想法
I would love to know what the smarter versions of me think.
好吧
Okay.
第一个威尔斯告诉我
The first Wells told me
我有一天会
my time would come
成为英雄
to be a hero,
我的职责就是在那一天
that it was my job to show up,
做好准备  展示自己
to be ready for when it did.
知道我为什么喜欢在这里工作吗
You know why I love working here?
为什么
Why?
我们都在互相投资
We're all making investments in each other.
我在你身上投资了
I made an investment in you,
有一天这项投资会得到回报
and one day, that investment's gonna pay off
当你用...
when you use that...
你疯狂的思考方式来帮助我
crazy way of thinking you have to help me out.
如果他在这里  他会说
I guess if he were here, he would say,
"展现自己"
"Show up""
做好准备
Be ready.
因为...
'Cause...
有一天  你可能要救我
one day, you might need to save my ass.
照这个速度  你很快就能每小时跑3700公里
Keep it up at this rate, you're gonna reach Mach 3 soon.
我知道  我这么短时间能达到
I know, it's--it's crazy how fast I've gotten
-这速度  很疯狂吧  -是的
- in such a short time, right? - Yeah.
我需要你再加快更多
And I'm gonna need you to get a lot faster.
为什么
Why is it?
因为经过我反复计算
Because I have done the math over and over,
终于发现我一直搞错了事情的方向
I finally realized that I have been looking at things the wrong way.
不是我从萨维塔手中拯救爱瑞丝
I'm not gonna save Iris from Savita,
而是你
you're.